=Love Actually S5 Extra Episode=
Coming.
So, ready?
I'm ready.
Looks nice.
Here we are.
You went straight for that one, huh?
Yeah.
Do you want to use this?
The way I'm pushing feels awkward.
(Off to a bad start)
I feel like
my trajectory is wrong.
Why is it awkward?
Let me take a look.
Alright, coach.
Personal training will cost you.
Is this too tight for you?
You can...
Yeah, move it up a bit.
Don't you need a wider grip?
Let me see.
Too heavy for you?
No.
Really?
You think it's too heavy.
You're talking too much.
I'm dying of laughter.
Wait, let me see.
I think something is off.
But I can't tell what it is.
What's off?
How did you do it?
Well.
I'll call it a general workout.
I can spot you.
Then go ahead.
One more rep.
One more.
Reward you with one more.
That's really not necessary.
One more rep.
Reward yourself with one more.
Reward me with one more.
Reward everyone with one more.
Go away.
What's next?
What are you doing next?
I'll have this in the middle.
Okay.
This one works really well.
Then do this.
Me first?
You go first.
Do one?
Okay.
Let me catch my breath.
Then I'll go first. Get down.
This is a bit high for me, isn't it?
Maybe it's okay.
That's too light.
Don't make me laugh.
"Idiot."
Don't.
When you train by yourself,
you can make these sounds.
Don't do it
when I'm training.
Why doesn't it sound like before?
I'm dying of laughter.
You're just messing with me.
I didn't make it to twelve.
But you messed with me earlier.
You drained my energy.
I drained your energy?
It wasn't me who drained your energy.
(Actually, when he's working out,)
(he looks really focused.)
(When I watched him train,)
(I found the veins on his arms
were popping.)
(I just took a look.)
Took a look at the veins.
Was it hot?
Of course, I looked because it was hot.
Awesome.
You're awesome.
You're amazing.
Come on.
What? Shoulders?
Why does 7.5 feel heavier?
7.5? That's too light.
It feels heavier.
Too light.
You don't even have a facial expression.
Keep going.
Are you fanning me?
I'll fan you just like you did earlier.
No.
You just did that to me.
Let me catch my breath.
No, you have to save me.
You have to save me.
How do I save you?
I, you...
Wait.
When you see I can't get up, save me.
Again.
I thought there was one more.
Can't do it anymore.
Can't do it anymore?
Can't do it anymore. Let's bail.
Let's go.
Let's go, babe.
Did you bring your earphones?
Yes.
Then I'll wear yours.
I just need my phone.
Why are you so spacey today?
Well, I have something on my mind today.
But my brain
can't keep up with my own rhythm.
You're a bit spacey today.
It's really a bit cold today.
Today we're going to do some crafts.
(Felting Republic)
Come play with wool.
Let's play with some wool.
This place is so cute.
It really is lovely.
Hello.
Welcome.
You can look around
and decide what to make.
It's really cute.
It's my first time seeing this too.
Make one of these.
And then make a teddy bear.
Because we used to have a Teddy.
I know.
And it passed away three years ago.
My mom is still very sad about it.
So I want to make a Teddy for her.
She'll be very happy to see it.
So one Teddy
and one of these.
Yeah.
So cute.
It's my first time doing this too.
It's different
from what you imagined, right?
But I actually understand the principle.
I think you really like this.
How do you know?
I like this one too.
I like all the pink ones.
This looks a lot like the sunset
we watched that day
on the lighthouse.
Right?
I think the perspective is great.
Exactly the same.
Look.
(Photo by Wang Yi)
Right?
Exactly the same.
That day at the lighthouse.
This is what I made.
You caught me.
We can take our seats now, right?
Later, you'll poke it like this.
Poke it in.
Don't you think this is like
the needle used
for drawing blood when we were kids?
Ready?
Ms. Wang, ready?
(Two childish goofs)
Okay, we're about to start.
Alright.
Okay.
Because I feel like
this is a bit like doing
a gold micro-needling at a beauty salon.
Just wait till I get you!
Little face.
You're quite humorous.
My patient here is almost done.
How's it going with yours?
I've given
my patient a double dose.
How is doing crafts
today different
from last time?
I think our relationship
has made a qualitative leap.
And it's not a little improvement.
You said love is like the first needle
of a knitting machine.
Everything's hard at the beginning,
but it gets smooth after that.
Do you still remember that saying?
How did you think of saying that?
I said it for you.
I feel like I'm poking right
into its heart every time.
Look, my patient isn't making a sound.
It's slightly dead.
You're amazing.
It has a shape.
You're also amazing.
Divine doctor.
Divine doctor Wang Tuo.
So this darker one
is a Chinese rural dog.
The three stray dogs we adopted later
are all mixed breeds.
Actually, that day,
seeing Brother wearing that outfit,
I missed Miumiu a bit.
Did it wear a brown outfit that day?
That very day
was its birthday.
I think
it's accompanying you
in another way.
When you think of it,
it is right there with you.
This is from that dog
collaboration series.
When I knew
it had a tumor, and I went to negotiate.
I think when my mom sees this tomorrow,
she'll cry.
Then we should give it to her
at the end.
We'll talk about happy things first.
Okay.
Don't you think it's very lively?
Very cute.
Really cute.
Getting cold.
No.
Just now, there was a moment
I really missed Miumiu.
I almost cried.
And the tears came out through my nose.
Because I held them back.
Because it really looks
exactly like it.
Its mouth was crooked.
Do you like it?
Cute.
So cute.
Hold it like this, right?
Let's go, babe.
Yeah, I need to cook that meat.
Well,
if I don't cook the mince,
we can't eat it tomorrow.
Okay, thanks, sir.
Thanks, sir.
Easy to walk?
Easy.
Watch your head.
No problem. Let's go.
Suddenly I feel a bit reluctant
to leave the house.
You've been quite sentimental lately.
It's fine.
You're in Shanghai anyway.
When you're lonely,
come back and visit often.
Who else would be in the house?
Nobody.
Just the two of us.
Guessed for a long time.
Should we start the soup first?
Then I'll start the soup first.
And then,
it's really cold.
Really cold.
Are you cold?
Why don't you put on a jacket?
No, I mean today
it is indeed cold.
Not that I'm cold.
Then I'll turn on the AC.
Okay.
Babe, give me a hand.
I'll do it.
Do you know how?
Yes.
Then take one.
I'll handle the rest.
We have such a cozy domestic vibe,
Mr. Lu.
I think so too.
Do you like this peaceful,
homely atmosphere?
I'm thinking of the day we cooked
at Sanya again.
I was so happy.
Two people, four dishes.
Five dishes and a soup.
Waiting for the kids to come back.
Your husband is singing.
("Husband" on the music player)
He's my ex-husband.
Your ex-husband is now
singing for you.
Not together for you.
Thank you for being my sous-chef.
It's my pleasure.
Thank you for cooking for me.
That's my pleasure.
Cooking only for you
is the happiest thing.
Smells amazing.
Dig in.
It's been a while
since I made mapo tofu.
Half for each.
You eat half first.
Thanks, babe.
It's been a while.
I'm a bit worried.
I never worry when you cook.
(Chen Danqi comes home from work)
No one's here.
What are you doing?
I'm drawing a little portrait.
What's this?
Ruita (Wang Yi) made pork rib soup.
It's so good.
When did this appear?
Just made it.
Tonight.
On the table.
Have a bowl.
It's so good.
Let me try a bite.
Super delicious.
Have a bite.
You were home today?
I went to pick up Lizheng
from work today.
And then we went for a meal.
That's nice.
I went to a fashion week event
this afternoon.
After the event,
I worked.
Pure work.
I also really want to work.
You have to go back
to Beijing for work, right?
No, my work is in Hangzhou.
Yeah, Changsha.
I barely have any work in Beijing.
So you and Ji Yu
can meet often.
Do you know
why I
cried
so hard?
Because Ji Yu really
can accurately
see my inner feelings
and he pointed them out.
What did he point out?
He said,
"I often see
you spacing out at the dinner table.
I knew at that moment you must..."
Right on the spot,
I said how you found that.
I find him so sensitive
and so warm.
When we talked last time,
we reached a consensus
that we're both highly sensitive.
Are you too?
But
sometimes I'm a bit thick-skinned.
So it's selective high sensitivity.
But actually,
I overthink and get sad easily.
Really?
But I feel like
you have grown
into a very strong person.
I think
I was more sensitive when I was a kid.
When I was a kid, I was like
having very fragile skin.
And now,
the skin has thickened.
And I've also learned
when to apply sunscreen,
when to apply allergy medicine,
and when to choose
to put on makeup and go out.
That's the feeling.
I think you've really grown up well.
I've re-raised yourself.
I'm still highly sensitive,
but I choose to be more sensitive
where I seek inspiration.
As for other aspects,
I try not to be too sensitive.
If I'm too sensitive,
it'll be a disaster.
A total disaster.
How do you feel in the house?
I'm actually quite happy.
Don't you have
any emotional fluctuations?
I have.
I do have.
Actually, a while ago,
I was crying a lot.
Because I felt
too many intense emotions from everyone.
I can feel when someone is happy
and when someone is unhappy.
I can feel when someone is torn,
and when he is
very joyful
or very hesitant.
I can feel all of that.
So I actually
feel not only my own emotions.
When I feel all of that,
I just keep crying.
I was like that for a while before.
Later,
it got better.
Now I can control it.
Actually, I think love is
that though you like being with him
and you like him,
you need to leave
a lot of energy for yourself.
If you're always trying
to figure him out,
and your heart is with him...
I mean, if your heart is up in the air,
never at peace,
you'll become unstable.
And your energy
will keep...
Going outward.
So you need to pull it back inward.
Otherwise, before this relationship
is even finished,
you'll be
exhausted in the early stages.
Mentally drained.
Before he has even noticed anything,
you may have burnt yourself
out from overthinking.
Tired to death.
I can't afford to get emotional.
Once I get emotional, I get distorted.
Your actions get distorted.
When I'm not emotional, I'm fine.
Actually, what I want to say is
that women here
basically
have our own
independent side in life
or in our careers.
But the reason we're still single
at this age
must be because
we're emotionally weaker.
That is to say,
all our strengths
are very long.
And our love
is this short.
So what can we do?
At work, we don't need the short one.
In work, this is enough.
As for this shortcoming,
we ultimately have to learn and grow.
So if there's something to learn,
learn it.
If we can, learn it.
If there's nothing to learn...
Just don't learn.
Just don't.
(Jiaxing)
Let's go for a walk in the sun.
Walk the dogs.
Okay.
We're off to walk the dogs.
Going for a stroll.
You can tell the three are very happy.
Yeah, they are especially happy.
For these three dogs,
people said when they were strays,
they looked really bad.
After joining us, they became...
Handsome boys and pretty girls.
Handsome boys and pretty girls,
like princesses and princes.
As if reborn.
Yeah, a happy dog's life.
Jiutiao is emotionally stable, right?
But when it walks,
it'll sway.
A little bit, yeah.
Because it's a female.
It's a female.
Watch out for the little one.
(Yielding to dogs)
The little dog also wants to be petted.
Scooped up in one go.
Were you afraid of dogs
when you were little?
I was afraid of dogs when I was little.
Me too.
But I think
dogs can tell you're afraid of them.
And the more afraid you are,
the more they come and tease you.
There are so many dogs here.
There are lots of dog friends here.
Dog friends.
Do they all know each other?
No.
They're also here to walk their dogs.
They can make friends.
That white one
is a Samoyed, right?
Smiling.
Among dogs, Samoyeds are known
as smiling angels.
This little Teddy.
It sees our dogs.
Dog party.
Look, the weather is so nice.
Lots of dogs on the grass.
Feeling good.
Good.
Okay, be good. Okay.
Let's go.
Let's go, Jiutiao.
Did you put on sunscreen today?
No.
It's okay.
Get more sun.
The sun is so good.
This is cosmic energy.
Okay, get more sun.
No more sunscreen next time.
Now you're being excluded.
Soon the discipline director will ask
what they are doing.
I feel like they want to kiss right now.
I think they want to kiss.
You two, let go of your hands.